*  English عربى Deutsch Dutch English Español فارسی Français Indonesia Italiano 日本語 한국어 Polski Português Русский ไทย Türkiye Tiếng Việt 繁體中文 简体中文

 عربى Deutsch Dutch English Español فارسی Français Indonesia Italiano 日本語 한국어 Polski Português Русский ไทย Türkiye Tiếng Việt 繁體中文 简体中文

**

Privacy Policy
==============

**

* 
* 
* 
* 

What personal data we collect
-----------------------------

GIGA-BYTE Technology Co., Ltd. is the ‘Controller’ of the personal data you provide to us. We only collect basic personal data about you which does not include any special types of information or sensitive information. This does however include your email, and sometimes your name and address.

Why we need it
--------------

We need to know your basic personal data in order to provide you with services such as:  
•product trouble shooting  
•warranty inquiries  
•repair services  
•product purchase and shipment  
•product registration  
•entry to contests, sweepstakes or giveaways  
•product rebates  
•entry to online gaming events  
• contents you may be interested in  
• access to user forums  
We will not collect any personal data from you that we do not need in order to provide and oversee these services to you.

With your consent
-----------------

If you have consented to receive product news/promotional offers from us, we will send such content to the email address you have provided. However you may choose to opt out of receiving such emails anytime via your profile settings or by following the opt-out instructions embedded in the emails.

GIGABYTE Community
------------------

Gigabyte Community is provided as a service to enable GIGABYTE members to interact with each other. Data collected when you access Gigabyte Community includes：  
(1) User data：name, nationality, e-mail address.  
(2) Non user data：content you post in Gigabyte Community, including but not limited to articles, pictures, photos, audio/video, interaction with other members.  
(3) Usage data：personal data that is collected about you when you’re accessing and/or using Gigabyte Community, including: IP addresses, visiting time, location, the type of web browser and the version, operation system, page view, breadcrumbs, language, click behavior and its corresponding time.

Social logins
-------------

If you login or register on any of our websites using credentials of a third party social media network such as Facebook or Twitter, you authorize us to collect your authentication information, which is generally limited to your name/username, e-mail address, and encrypted access credentials. We store/use such information as explained in this privacy statement. However, we are not responsible for the terms of use and privacy policies for any of these third party social media networks. Please visit their websites for more information about their privacy policies and terms of use.

Sharing with 3rd parties
------------------------

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

How we store your data
----------------------

All the personal data we process is processed by our staff in Taiwan and the IT hosting and maintenance of this information is located on servers within Taiwan. We have a Data Protection regime in place to oversee the effective and secure processing of your personal data. We will keep your basic personal data (name, address, contact details) for 5 years after the last user activity, after which time it will be destroyed.

Cookies
-------

Cookies are small data files sent to your browser when you visit a site. We use cookies to do the following:  
•Log you in to our services  
•Remember preferences and settings  
•Better understand how people are using our services, and improve and promote those services based on that information  
  
You can manage your cookie preferences by clicking on 'Cookie Settings' at the bottom right of our website or adjusting settings in your browser to opt-out of cookies. However, choosing to do so may limit certain website functionalities.  
  
Please note: Necessary cookies, essential for the proper operation of the website, are set without requiring your permission. Other types of cookies need your consent before they can be set; however, opting out may also reduce certain website functionalities.  

Third-Party Analytics, Advertising and Functionality Tracking Cookies
---------------------------------------------------------------------

Unless you choose to turn off Analytics, Advertising and/or Functionality cookies, our website utilizes tracking cookies from other third parties. Analytics cookies collect data about how you interact with our website, this data helps us improve and enhance your experience for our website. Advertising cookies allow us to recognize you on third-party websites, and enable us to show you personalized content there. For example, if you visit one of our website pages, you may later see an ad for Aorus or GIGABYTE products when you visit a tech news site. Functionality cookies allow us to remember your preferences and choices, improving usability and make our website more tailored to you.  
When you choose to turn off Analytics, Advertising and/or Functionality cookies, third-party cookies will not track your activity nor collect any data based on your choice. If you accept Analytics, Advertising and/or Functionality cookies when you initially visit the website, you can still turn off these Analytics, Advertising and/or Functionality cookies at any time later by clicking on 'Cookie Settings' at the bottom right of our website or adjusting settings in your browser to opt-out of cookies.  
  
The third-party Analytics tracking cookies we use are:  
• Google Analytics : Google Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google that tracks and reports on website traffic and user behavior.  
• Yandex Metrica : Yandex Metrica is a web analytics service provided by Yandex. It offers a range of tools and features, helping us analyze and optimize our websites.  
• VWO A/B Testing : VWO A/B Testing is a tool for optimizing websites by analyzing the performance of different versions through A/B testing. It helps us gain a deeper understanding of user experiences and allows us to build and maintain our services based on user feedback. For information on opting out of VWO, please refer to [this link](https://vwo.com/opt-out/) .  
• Microsoft Clarity : Clarity is a behavioral analysis tool provided by Microsoft that helps us understand user interaction with the website. Clarity’s features like browsing session recordings and heatmaps provide us feedback that will be used to enhance our website for you. The data Clarity collects is de-identified and anonymous. For more information about how Microsoft collects and uses your data, visit the [Microsoft Privacy Statement](https://privacy.microsoft.com/privacystatement) .  
• LinkedIn : We use cookies set by LinkedIn to measure the performance of our website in order to improve the overall user experience. For more information about how LinkedIn collects and uses your data, visit [here](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-policy) .  
• Akamai Boomerang : Akamai Boomerang is an open source JavaScript library for user monitoring. It measures the performance characteristics of page loads and interactions. For more information about Akamai Boomerang, visit [here](https://techdocs.akamai.com/home/page/manage-cookie-preferences) .  
  
The third-party Advertising tracking cookies we use are:  
• Google Ads : Google Ads is an online advertising platform developed by Google. It allows us to create and manage ads that appear on Google’s search results pages and across its vast network of partner sites.  
• Facebook Pixels : Facebook Pixel is a tool provided by Meta that allows us to track and optimize our Facebook ad campaigns. It collects data on how you interact with our site and how you respond to our ads.  
• YouTube : We use cookies set by YouTube to process behavioral data from users and the YouTube video server, such as video playback, recommended content, and user behavior tracking, etc. For more information about how YouTube collects and uses your data, visit [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies#how-google-uses-cookies) .  
• LinkedIn : We use cookies set by LinkedIn to gather information about how ads perform and how you interact with ads. For more information about how LinkedIn collects and uses your data, visit [here](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-policy) .  
  
The third-party Functionality tracking cookies we use are:  
• LinkedIn : We use cookies set by LinkedIn to remember information about your browser and your preferences. For more information about how LinkedIn collects and uses your data, visit [here](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-policy) .  
• YouTube : We use cookies set by YouTube to measure bandwidth to determine whether users have access to the new or old player interface. For more information about how YouTube collects and uses your data, visit [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies#how-google-uses-cookies) .  

Children's online privacy protection
------------------------------------

Our service is not provided to children under the age of 13 years. We do not knowingly collect personal data from children under 13 years or under the applicable age limit. If we learn that we have collected the personal data of a child under the age of 13 years, we will take reasonable steps to delete the personal data.

What are your rights?
---------------------

If you wish to correct, modify, or deleted your personal data, you may do so through the settings in your profile in the applicable platform. Where profile settings are not accessible/applicable, or if you wish to raise a complaint /question on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact our Data Manager at [mydata@gigabyte.com](mailto:mydata@gigabyte.com) .

Updating this Privacy Policy
----------------------------

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The changes will not be retroactive, and the most current version of the Privacy Policy can always be found [here](https://profile.gigabyte.com/PrivacyPolicy.aspx) . We will try to notify you of material revisions, for example via a service notification or an email to the email associated with your account.

©2024 GIGA-BYTE Technology Co., Ltd. All rights reserved.　 |  [Terms of Use](https://profile.gigabyte.com/TermsOfUse.aspx)  |  [Privacy Policy](https://profile.gigabyte.com/PrivacyPolicy.aspx)  [](https://www.facebook.com/GIGABYTEofficial/)[](https://www.youtube.com/user/GIGABYTEChannel/)[](https://www.instagram.com/gigabyte_official/)[](https://www.linkedin.com/company/gigabyte/)
